# **Eric Kongkaew**

www.linkedin.com/in/erickongkaew erickongkaew@gmail.com • https://www.erikmoxley.com/ (978) 935-8860 • Greater Boston, MA 01851

#### **SUMMARY**

Passionate Software Engineer with 6+ months of experience working professionally as a developer creating unique websites and web apps for local and nation-wide businesses. 12+ years as a Former Manager of Pharmacy and Retail Operations, Project Manager, and Supervisor in the Pharmaceutical industry with past experiences of high-level management in planning, resourcing, and execution of major projects.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS**

HTML5 • CSS3 • Sass • Bootstrap • JavaScript • GitHub • Version Control • VSCode • Netlify • Heroku MySQL • Express • ReactJS • NodeJS • NPM • NextJS • Atlassian • Jira • Asana

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **PHOENIX AFTERGLOW - Burlington, MA**

# **Software Developer**

Mar 2022 - Present

- Design, develop and establish user-friendly, responsive, SEO optimized live websites and web-based applications for local and nation-wide businesses within industries such as: Specialty Trade Contractors, Retailers, Restaurants, Health & Wellness, Hospitality, Real Estate, Home Improvement, Travel, etc
- Maintain 30+ current clients' products through feature requests, bug fixes, integrations and enhancements
- Integrate back-end eCommerce into multiple websites with full shopping cart and payment functionalities
- Revamped company procedures, HR guidelines, policies and workflows to assist with growth of business
- Built high-end work PCs, upgraded software, and introduced industry relevant tools for increased productivity and functionality during each project's life cycle
- Technologies, tools and other skills used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Sass, GitHub, React, NextJS, NodeJS, Express, MySQL, PHP, Microsoft Office, Agile/Scrum, Asana, Google Analytics, FTP, Adobe Creative Suite

# WALGREENS BOOTS ALLIANCE INTERNATIONAL/CO. - Greater Boston, MA

# Manager of Pharmacy and Retail Operations

Sep 2007 - May 2019

- Managed 25+ direct reports including Assistant Managers, Supervisors, Pharmacy Managers, Technicians, etc.
- Coached and mentored multiple Assistant Managers in passing the company's university and training program that eventually led to their promotions for the area
- Involved in creating efficient training procedures, templates, guidelines and tools used district wide which led to increased leadership engagement, improved on-boarding and an average employee retention increase by 25%
- Exceeded customer Net Promoter Score (75%+) & Rx patient care (78%+) targets 2 years in a row

#### **District Project Manager**

- Provided overall project management, strategy and oversight on major transformation project in merger with U.K. company that resulted in promotion to Manager of Retail and Pharmacy Operations
- Led district leadership team of 8 to implement new cosmetic lines such as No7/S&G into 8 locations in the area
- Participated in ~12 district meetings involving scope, cost, and timing to meet company and stakeholder expectations
- Managed communication, scheduling, budget of 2,600 hours, issue & risk managements, and other PMI functions
- Communicated with at least 8 vendor teams, small contractors and mid to large sized suppliers located on and offsite to accomplish project results

#### **Assistant Manager of Operations / Supervisor**

- Managed 15+ direct reports ranging from Pharmacy Tech Trainees to Customer Service Associates
- Utilized Kronos to maintain time cards and bi-weekly payroll; Workforce for scheduling, PTO and overall budgeting

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **COMPANY FULL STACK INPUTS PAGE**

Oct 2021

Full-Stack Web Development – HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express, NodeJS, MySQL, Express Validator LIVE: https://erikmoxley.github.io/fs-test-ek

SOURCE: https://github.com/ErikMoxley/fs-test-ek

- Front end built with HTML, CSS, JavaScript deployed on GitHub Pages using their domain
- Using a Node back end, submitted POST goes through ExpressJS deployed on Heroku
- Uses a MySQL database to receive POST requests and MySQL Workbench for admin to check data sent

NEXTJS BLOG Aug 2021 – Nov 2021

Front-End Web Development - NextJS, CSS, JavaScript, React Router Dom, Netlify Forms

LIVE: https://moxleydevblog.netlify.app

SOURCE: https://github.com/ErikMoxley/moxleydevblog

- Personal and developer blog page built with NextJS by Vercel, The React framework
- Markdown files are converted to posts using slug components sorted by date
- Contact page uses Netlify Forms CMS to manage and accept submissions, email notification once received

#### **MEDIAN AND AVERAGE INPUTS PAGE**

Jan 2022

Front-End Web Development - HTML, CSS, JavaScript

LIVE: https://erikmoxley.github.io/fe-test-inputs

SOURCE: https://github.com/ErikMoxley/fe-test-inputs

- Simple HTML form that displays back the average and median to the user from 3 inputs
- Front end validation. HTML integrated 'step' only allows positive integers to be used on submit

## **EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION**

• Zero to Mastery Academy • Udemy – Remote • www.github.com/erikmoxley

Software Engineering • Web Development • HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Sass, ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS, Git

• Learn Engage Advance Perform (LEAP) - Manchester, NH

May 2016

Business Management • Pharmaceutical Industry • WBA University for Drug Store Managers

• GROW InsideOut Development - Greater Boston, MA

Nov 2017

GROW model is one of the most used coaching models for Agile coaching and frameworks

#### **ADDITIONAL**

Volunteering:

VFW Foundation – Haverhill, MA	2018
Cystic Fibrosis – Haverhill, MA	2016 – 2018
<ul> <li>American Diabetes Association – Waltham, MA</li> </ul>	2016
Team Walk for Cancer Care - Lowell, MA	2015
<ul> <li>Community Action Council – Bedford, MA</li> </ul>	2021